hyves.org 2007-03-24

# Hyves.net - Always in touch with your friends

Last updated: 26 September 2004 

Hyves is a network of friends, we handle your information the way you would expect from a friend. Meaning: 

  * **No selling to third parties**  
We will never sell your address, email, mobile number nor any other personal information. You decide who may see what information (no one, only friends or everyone).. 
  * **No spam**  
We don't like spam and assume you don't, either. We will rarely bother you with information on new features. Please let us know if you do not wish to receive this information. 

Click here to set your email notifications. 

Passwords will be saved encrypted. No one – even at Hyves HeadQuarters! – will have access to them. 

**Personal information**  
Providing your personal information is not obliged. Some services, such as classifieds, may not be accessible without providing more information. 

Your personal information can be processed in various ways. This information includes for example your name, address, city, birth date, education, gender and emailaddress, but also your favorite brands or interests. You may have indicated that you’re interested in a subject, or your interests may show from the pages that you visit at Hyves. 

We use this information to adjust Hyves to your needs and interests. It may also be used to make advertisements more relevant to you. This way we want to shield male Hyvers from Always commercials, and female Hyvers from Gilette. (Don't worry, guys that are interested in Always can make their interest known to us) 

Of course we treat your information very carefully. Again, we treat you as you could expect from friends. (yes this sounds corny, but we mean it! :-) ) 

If you use a service from a partner, the privacy statement of that partner applies. Check their privacy statement when visiting their website. 

Finally we record IP addresses to find out from which computers Hyves is visited due to possible hack attempts. This data can also be used if Hyvers are being molested or in case of fake accounts, to reveal the identity of their stalkers. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small text files that are saved on your hard disk or in the memory of your computer. They can be used to save your preferences for a service, or to prevent you from seeing an advertisement too often. Cookies can’t damage your computer or files. 

If you don’t want to accept cookies you change the settings in your browser. Certain features may not be accessible with your cookies switched-off. 

In the future our privacy statement may be updated. The changes can then be found on this page, so we recommend you visit this page regularly. 

Privacy is a hot issue, and justly so. I hope we made it clear that this is extremely important to us. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to email me at Raymond @ hyves.net. 

Raymond Spanjar  
http://Raymond.hyves.net. [members@hyves.net](mailto:members@hyves.net)
